onlygowns.com 2009-06-19

# :: Only Gowns ::

**Revised as on 1, May 2004  
**  
OnlyGowns realize the importance of protecting the privacy of personal and financial information of its revered customers. We have framed a stringent set of guidelines, polices and security measures to secure this private arena of our valuable clientele. When you register online with OnlyGowns or use our online store, we ask you to give your consent to use and process your personal data in accordance with this online privacy policy. This privacy policy is valid for all users of this website.

**What information is collected by OnlyGowns?**

OnlyGowns collect personal data from visitors, who register their information or who use the online store on the website. We also use cookies (see more below) and track IP addresses to improve our services and enrich your experience.

**How is the information provided used by OnlyGowns?**

If you give your personal information, we will use this information to register you with our website, to administer our website services, and/or to process any orders you may place online. We will also send you announcements or communications by email provided you give us your permission by submitting your personal details. Otherwise, we use your information only to review our performance and to improve our services further. We will communicate you regarding your order if you have placed an online order

**Does OnlyGowns share your information with others?**

At OnlyGowns, we do not believe in selling, renting or disclosing clientele name, address, email address or any other personal information to other or non-OnlyGowns entity. We do not pass or disclose your private information to third party, unless subject to law or in connection with a legal claim or proceeding. However, if OnlyGowns is acquired by another entity, information pertaining to the clients of OnlyGowns may be made available to the new entity.

**Security**

OnlyGowns keep a tab or a check on every fraudulent means of getting information by implementing appropriate security measures. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form ask user to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number /or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. In spite of all possible ways and means to protect your valuable data, it is to be noted that no internet data transmission is guaranteed to be full-proof or secure from access by unintended intruders and hence we should not be held responsible for any breach of security unless this is due to our negligence.

**About Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information a web site can send to computer's browser for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to ascertain which web pages are visited and how often. These value-additions are helpful to make our web site more user friendly, interactive and above all provide you with a better experience and environment when you get back to our website again. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you do not need to accept them. To disable cookies, you should access the "help" tab on your browser or read the information that came with your browser software. However, your visit to our website will be significantly enhanced if cookies are not disabled.

**Log Files** OnlyGowns use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information **.  
**   
**Acceptance of Privacy Policy and Modifications**

By accessing and using the OnlyGowns website, you give us your consent to collect, use and disclose your information as described in this privacy policy. OnlyGowns reserve the right to seldom make changes to its privacy policy or practices. It is therefore in your own interest to review this page from time to time to keep yourself informed and get updated information including in particular, each time you use the online shop. We will notify you about any changes in our privacy policy by posting the modifications on our website.

**Contact Us**

In case of any comments or queries regarding our privacy policy, email us at: [ customersupport@onlygowns.com](mailto:customersupport@onlygowns.com)

.
